<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BioApp</string>
    <string name="walton_name">Walton Hi-Tech Industries PLC</string>
    <string name="walton_bio">\n<b>1977</b>
        \nOur story begins in 1977 along the unforgiving, high-paced and everchanging roads of Paltan, the heart of Puran (Old) Dhaka. It was here where “Rezve and Brothers” started its journey pioneered by Alhaj SM Nazrul Islam, the loving father and grand-father of our honorable Directors. Later on, our honorable vice-chairman of WALTON Hi-Tech Industries Limited, S. M. Nurul Alam Rezvi joined the venture with a goal to expanding the family business to new levels. He had a rebellious spirit and a lofty objective to change the export-import scenario of Bangladesh. When the whole country was solely depending upon appliances imported from overseas, Mr. Rezvi dreamt of changing the market by building a self-reliant, 100% locally produced appliance factory and with this in mind he included his four brothers into the company. These five hardworking, farsighted young men worked tirelessly to give life to their brainchild and had manifested a renaissance throughout the years so WHIL could take shape.
        \n\n<b>2006-2015</b>
        \nThe actual path for WHIL to ascend as the leading E&amp;E company in Bangladesh was paved on April 17th ,2006 when it was incorporated under the companies act, 1994. The business was commenced in 2008 and exporting started soon after from 2011. Signing of agreement between WHIL and DEG, KFW Germany in 2015, was a giant leap for the export industry in Bangladesh.
        \n\n<b>2017</b>
        \nEvery idea starts with a problem. Our problem was simple: the E&amp;E industry in Bangladesh was 100% dependent on import. The solution, simpler: manufacture everything in our country and meet the prevalent E&amp;E demand. With this in mind, factories to produce refrigerators, air conditioners, televisions and motorcycles were established in Chandra, Gazipur in 2007 and with unimaginable success in business our pioneers build the first ever compressor manufacturing plant in Bangladesh in 2017. The goal of meeting customer demand was reached in 2016, when more than 60% of the total market share was led by Walton Refrigerators and Home Appliances. With this we could proudly say we implemented the solution to our problem, successfully.
        \n\n<b>2018-2020</b>
        \nWHIL has hoisted the red and green flag in the global market from the beginning of its existence having import business with more than 40 countries including India, Nepal, Bhutan, Myanmar, Maldives, United Arab Emirates, Qatar, Nigeria, West Africa, Australia, Europe, USA, South Africa, Singapore, Poland, Romania, Saudi Arabia, Sri Lanka and many more. From the beginning of our business, the Government and regulatory bodies of the People\'s Republic of Bangladesh has availed constant support and has an active role to pivot WALTON to its prime. With a view to reimburse to the country\'s economy, WHIL was enlisted as a PLC or Public Limited Company on May 14th, 2018 and started trading with DSE &amp; CSE from September 23rd, 2020.
        \n\n<i><b>VISION 2030</b></i>
        \nWALTON has become a common household name in Bangladesh and we are working to imbed the scenario globally. Our goal is to become one of the top 5 leading E&amp;E brands, globally, within the year 2030. In the age of globalization, urbanization and capitalization, WHIL reminds that there are alternative ways to revest to the world, and the people around us: through spurring and giving life to our utopian imagination.</string>

</resources>